There's a lot of going on [music] in the
world all the time.
>> It's unethical to bring children into
the world given the current state it's
in.
>> I [music] mean, our grandparents went
through world wars. Surely the world
wasn't in a better state back then. I
also feel whatever's going on out there
in the world is going to have less of an
impact compared to the immediate
environment a child is in. And that's
what would make a bigger difference in
whether a child grows up happy and
[music] resilient. But if someone has
thought about it and they're not
confident that they can provide the kind
of environment, that's why they've
decided the most ethical thing for them
to do is to not [music] have children. I
think they made a perfectly valid
decision for themselves. But I still
wouldn't agree that bringing children
into this world is [music] inherently
unethical or irresponsible.